whyfame.com 2010-01-16

# WhyFame.com: Privacy Policy

**WhyFame Privacy Policy** The following privacy statement covers the WhyFame.com website. Please read this statement regarding our websites. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us. 

**Ownership of Information** WhyFame.com is the sole owner of the information collected on the WhyFame.com website. 

**Third Party Cookies** Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, WhyFame.com has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by WhyFame.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. If you do not want to allow information to be collected through the use of cookies, you can generally opt out of providing this information by setting your browser to reject cookies or by using the [Network Advertising](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) web site. 

**Third Party Advertising** The ads appearing on WhyFame.com are delivered to users by third party advertisers including Google, among others. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

**Comments** In order to enhance their use of the WhyFame.com website, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. WhyFame.com does not endorse these comments as they are opinions of users not associated with WhyFame.com or its employees. 

**Mailing List** WhyFame.com may launch a mailing list for WhyFame.com website. In order to sign up to receive regular emails from a site’s mailing list, users must submit information including a valid email address and demographic information such as location and interests. This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list will receive regular emails from the site, including new articles added to the site as well as emails from third party site sponsors. If you do not wish to receive emails from third party advertisers, do not sign up for the mailing list. 

**Public Forums** This website makes chat rooms and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Log Files** Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement. 

**Legal Disclaimer** Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, WhyFame.com may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on WhyFame.com 

**Business Transitions** In the event WhyFame.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, user personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. 

**External Links** WhyFame.com contain links to other sites. Please be aware that WhyFame.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by WhyFame.com 

**Notification of Changes** Whenever WhyFame.com changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate. 

**Contact Information** If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
